8/28/2020 Alex Bezek - Resume

Alex Bezek Associate Lead Software Engineer

Email: alex.liam.bezek@gmail.com Linkedin: Linkedin Mobile: 913-626-1909

Personal Profile

I've been a Software Engineer at Cerner for the past 6 years. During that time I've been responsible for creating and maintaining React + Rails Applications and Microservices as a Team Lead and Individual Contributor working with containerization, CI/CD, alerting and monitoring, and infrastructure management. I'm passionate about good developer tooling, automation, and service orchestration.

Work Experience

Associate Lead Software Engineer

Sept 2019 - Present

Currently I work as a technical lead for key projects, and an individual contributor on strategic projects. I often tackle initiatives for deployment changes and new operational requirements first, creating dev tooling, documentation, and a repeatable process for other teams to consume.

Team Lead I Senior Software Engineer

Mar 2017 - Sept 2019

I was as a team lead with direct reports and a Product Owner for a React on Rails based application. I met with vendors, clients, and other stake holders to gather requirements for the team to implement. I volunteered for this to learn React as we didn't have any senior React Engineers.

Software Engineer - Associate Software Engineer

Jun 2014 – Mar 2017

I started as an individual contributor adding features to new Rails Apps and Services. During this time Docker and the Container Wars were blossoming and I spent my free time exploring these systems. I joined a second team on the side to be involved with the initial Docker Automated deployments project and CI/CD pipelines using Jenkins and Spinnaker.

Key Projects

- Worked with Jenkins, Docker, and Spinnaker to create CI/CD pipelines for hundreds of Rails Apps and Services to use to deploy across multiple clouds.
- Multiple projects on Observability and Performance like automating New Relic and Splunk alerts, enhancements for better distributed tracing, and product KPI and Error Budget Analysis.
- Pioneered deployments for our team to the AWS Cloud for the first time and worked through multiple waves to seamlessly migrate hundreds of clients workloads to those AWS datacenters without downtime.

https://my-pi.alexbezek.me

8/28/2020 Alex Bezek - Resume

 Tech Lead for our Vanity Domain feature allowing Clients to configure custom domain names for our apps with SSL Certificates automated via ACM

 Created a custom Terraform Provider in Go for our internal services to manage service configurations in source control.

Awards

Site Reliability Engineering Spotlight Cerner Masters Leadership - Dev Achievement Award

Education

Kansas State University

2009-2014

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Computer Software Engineering

Fun

To learn more about Nrgok, I decided to use this as an excuse to play with it. I setup Ngrok V1 on an EC2 instance behind an ALB using a Certificate and Domain I own. My Rasberry-Pi is running the Nrok client connecting to it and serving this file. If you have the v1 Ngrok client, you can connect with the following config.yml file

server_addr: alexbezek.me:4443 trust_host_root_certs: true

https://my-pi.alexbezek.me